<system>
  <title>
    WOW
  </title>
  <acronym-expansion>
    War On Words
  </acronym-expansion>
  <short-description>
    A text filter/web proxy that rewrites propaganda.
  </short-description>
  <medium-description>
    <p>
      WOW wants  to make people say  WOW when they  see how linguistic
      rewriting changes the meaning and they realize that the media is
      intentionally   confusing  different   concepts  to   their  own
      advantage.   Even as  someone  who has  read  numerous books  on
      counter-propaganda this system was an eye-opener!
    </p>
  </medium-description>
  <long-description>
    <p>
      It doesn't make sense to do such a thing because the functioning
      of the propaganda is at a much different level.
    </p>
    <p>
      Media is inherently biased.   Often times, there is an intention
      and a desire to manipulate (often in a deceptive, counterfactual
      or psychologically  operative fashion) the  cognitive process of
      the  reader  to  obtain some  behavioral/operational  semantics.
      Therefore,  this  service  rewrites  web  pages  to  conform  to
      terminological  standards   representative  of  some  particular
      worldview  or  perspective  (including  so  far  as  to  include
      "foreign" languages).  It has been suggested to call this system
      metabias.
    </p>
    <p>
      War on Words substitutes  various expressions in common use that
      have deceptive  effects.  The only  lesson here is  really this:
      Perhaps you  need not  know what  is in the  library if  you can
      understand why some people would want to burn it down!
    </p>
    <p>
      In otherwords  this is a very  direct counter-propaganda system.
      There are  more sophisticated ones  but we have not  bothered to
      create  them because  they  would likely  be  misused.  This  is
      somewhat likely  to be misused, especially  when they completely
      control the media with DRM and so forth.
    </p>
    <p>
      There  are various  attacks  that  can be  used  against such  a
      content post filter, and should be guarded against.
    </p>
    <p>
      Oftentimes they will not  include enough information in order to
      disambiguate  the actual  meaning  which makes  it difficult  to
      understand.
    </p>
  </long-description>
</system>